#### Contact

josedavids123@live.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jose-davidsauma-zaretsky-171b3823b (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Java Development Spring Data MySQL

### Certifications

Certificado Backend Con Java

# Jose David Sauma Zaretsky

Junior Java Software Developer | Java - SpringMVC-REST - Spring Security - PHP- MySQL - JDBC/JPA - JUnit - Git | Recruiter Medellín, Antioquia, Colombia

### Summary

Como reclutador bilingüe con 2 años de experiencia especializado en reclutamiento masivo y financiero en el sector BPO, he desarrollado un profundo entendimiento de las dinámicas del talento en el ámbito empresarial. Además de mi experiencia en recursos humanos, soy un apasionado desarrollador Java con experiencia en tecnologías como SpringMVC, REST, Spring Security, PHP, MySQL, JDBC/JPA, JUnit y Git. Mi capacidad para fusionar la visión estratégica del reclutamiento con habilidades técnicas en el desarrollo de software me permite comprender a fondo las necesidades de mi equipo y garantizar un ajuste perfecto entre talento y proyectos. Estoy comprometido con el crecimiento profesional continuo y la creación de equipos altamente eficientes y colaborativos. ¡Conéctemos y exploremos nuevas oportunidades juntos!, podrias darmelo en ingles

As a bilingual recruiter with 2 years of specialized experience in high-volume and financial recruitment within the BPO sector, I have developed a profound understanding of talent dynamics in the business environment. In addition to my human resources background, I am a passionate Java developer with expertise in technologies such as SpringMVC, REST, Spring Security, PHP, MySQL, JDBC/JPA, JUnit, and Git. My ability to merge the strategic vision of recruitment with technical skills in software development allows me to thoroughly grasp the needs of my team and ensure a perfect alignment between talent and projects. I am committed to continuous professional growth and the creation of highly efficient and collaborative teams. Let's connect and explore new opportunities together!

Experience

Freelance (Self employed)
Freelance Software Developer
October 2023 - Present (1 year)

Medellín Metropolitan Area

Various projects as a Freelancer developer

iQor

Recruiter

November 2022 - Present (1 year 11 months)

Medellín, Antioquia, Colombia

Solvo Global

Recruiter

May 2022 - November 2022 (7 months)

Armada Nacional de Colombia

Military Service

April 2021 - April 2022 (1 year 1 month)

Coveñas, Sucre, Colombia

Solvo Global

**Collections Specialist** 

September 2020 - April 2021 (8 months)

Medellín, Antioquia, Colombia

Teleperformance

**Customer Service Agent** 

March 2019 - January 2020 (11 months)

Bogota, D.C., Capital District, Colombia

## Education

Globant University

Computer Software and Media Applications · (February 2023 - February 2024)

Politécnico de Colombia

Technician, Computer Software Technology/Technician · (July

2022 - December 2023)

Politécnico de Colombia

Diploma of Education, Computer Software and Media Applications · (November 2022 - March 2023)

## Colegio Retos

High School Diploma · (January 2017 - December 2018)